As a solo developer or small startup,
you do spend time thinking about what
you're building before you start
building. VIP coding changed that
completely. Even as a solo developer,
I'm able to build something in an hour,
but I'm often left thinking, hey, what
did I build? What were some of the
decisions I made? Cuz you move so fast,
get a response. You're like, well, I
don't quite like that. I'd like it to do
this instead. And the back and forth
with the agent sometimes is basically a
stream of consciousness. So, that's the
core problem space we were looking to
solve with Hero. We're not looking to
just build yet another agentic editor.
Inspectdriven development is the
approach we think will be the way
everyone develops with AI going forward.
>> What are the some of the key learnings
that you have took from this journey of
learning about specifications?
Specifications are combinations,
artifacts in hero product, but high
level they're about behavior and a
learning is they need to be composable
documents with really functional
business use cases as well as code
pseudo code people can put in there,
technical diagrams, behaviors around
error handling, behaviors around
properties.
>> How do you see people in future wanting
to use specifications?
>> Uh, okay. So that's a very deep
question.
[Music]
Hello and welcome to another episode of
the AI Native Dev. My name is Simon
Maple and I'm your host for today. And
today is going to be a fun episode.
We're going to be talking very much
about specd driven development but also
uh looking at and seeing a new pretty
cool tool actually on the market which
has been very recent uh called Kira. And
Kira is well I'll let the folks here uh
introduce it but it's a specd driven way
of being able to build software uh in
your IDE um which is very very
interesting and and we're going to go
into a few pieces talking about the
philosophy of specdriven development
show a demo of of uh Kira working and
then talk a little bit about the journey
that the folks had at AWS in order to
get to where we are today. So uh let me
introduce Nikil Swaminathan and Richard
Thrrell. Hey folks, how are you doing?
>> Hey Simon, doing great.
>> Doing good. Thanks for having us on.
>> So So let's jump into into into what you
what your roles are at Kira. Nikl, why
don't we start with yourself?
>> Sure. Uh I'm the product lead for Kuro.
So I've been now on the Kuro team for
the past 6 months or so, though it feels
like I've been here for years at this
point. And uh my job is to uh one help
build out what features we need to we
need to build and and and and two uh
work with the team on making sure we're
doing the right thing.
>> Awesome. And and Kira is around 19 sorry
a year and a half. Is it is that is that
fair to say? Year and a half in in in
build time.
>> Yeah, close to that. Um I I think let's
see it's July about 13 months actually.
Yeah. So I'm I'm Richard. I'm an
engineer on the Kuro team. Um uh I've
I've been as as Nickel kind of alluded
to uh I was I think either the first or
the second uh engineer that's um on the
team when we started it. Um and so I've
been involved in all phases of Kirro
development. Um but specifically, no p
pun intended, I actually focus the
majority of my time on specs. Um
including uh the original research
projects with a lot of the Amazon
science teams.
>> Amazing. So looking forward to getting
deeper into that. Let's we've we've said
Kira a few times. My my introduction
probably uh probably didn't do it
justice. Um why why don't we jump into
into what is Kira? Um Nikil, why don't
you why don't you walk us through give
us the definition of what the what Ko
problem Kuro is trying to solve?
>> The elevator pitch. Yeah. So uh Kira is
an agentic IDE that helps you do your
best work. That's our tagline. So let me
unpack that a little bit because that's
a little vague. So unless you've been
living under a rock the last year, year
and a half, um, agentic IDs have become
really popular, what are they? Agentic
IDs allow users to use natural language.
So developers use natural language to
interact with an agent to generate code
for an application. And what that
enabled is, you know, what used to take
us like days or week days or sometimes
even weeks to build a feature or
prototype uh has allowed us to build
this almost in hours now.
And what uh agentic ids really
popularized was the uh the term that we
all are very familiar with now called
vibe coding that really allows you to
use natural language and chat with an
agent to help you generate code for your
application. I think of vibe coding as
almost like chat GPT for coders, right?
You go back and forth with an agent to
build features out. And while vibe
coding has been great to help people get
up and running really quick, uh the
process does completely shortcircuit uh
traditional software development life
cycle best practices and how teams of
software engineers often work on a
day-to-day basis, right? Working on a
team here at Amazon and you know, prior
to Amazon, I I ran a startup, so I' I've
actually experienced both worlds. uh
when building a feature, you you often
spend days or if not weeks sometimes
detailing out requirements and designs
before you actually start coding. And
even as a solo developer or small
startup, you uh are definitely moving
faster cuz you you there's less
coordination, but you you do have you do
spend time thinking about what you're
building before you start start
building.
VIP coding kind of changed that
completely. uh right even as a solo
developer uh you know I'm able to build
something in an hour but after one
session of vibe coding I often find I'm
often left kind of thinking hey what did
I build what were some of the decisions
I made cuz I moved cuz you move so fast
right like you get you get a response
you're like well I don't quite like that
I'd like it I'd like it to do this
instead and and the the back and forth
with the agent sometimes is is basically
a stream of consciousness
and it takes you a minute to for you to
kind of reflect and think about hey what
did I actually get done? Uh so that
that's kind of the core problem space uh
we were looking to solve with hero.
We're not looking to just build yet
another agentic editor. Uh we really
think that the way you work with AI is
going to change and specri development
is the approach we think will will be
the way everyone develops with AI going
forward.
>> Yeah, really interesting. And I love the
way I love the kind of the the the way
you talk about how very often you you
very you sometimes make decisions but
that decision is then in your mind
versus you know you prompt it very very
quickly but you're actually not
capturing that and and while a lot of it
is represented as code when you're vibe
coding it's hard to then disseminate
afterwards well what is the decision and
what is just an implementation and if
you was to almost like think you know in
future if someone else was to come in
and look at your code you you could
somewhat guess what is decision, what is
meant to be, and what is an assumption,
and what is an LLM choice, but it's not
clear. It's it's it's a mixed kind of
reality in in code. So, that's what I
love about specs, the way it kind of
pulls that out and and and allows
individuals who who read that spec to to
to effectively understand what the
individual or or team that was
developing that is is is really adding
in.
>> Yeah. I know I was just saying one of
the analogies we I I use uh when talking
with people on on the team is that uh
it's it's vibe coding is almost like a
sometimes a slack thread where there's
like a stream of consciousness you know
there's often you know when you work
with teams there's really long slack
threads right where which have like 50
60 messages cuz they're you know
complicated topics that you're
discussing but then a lot of the
decision log is captured in that in that
thread versus a document you know where
you're like okay here's a document let's
review that document, make sure we're
aligned on that document before we
actually go implement it.
>> Yeah, really interesting. And the and
also like a a Slack message is a point
in time message and it is relevant at
that point based on the context that has
already passed and not on the context
that has has gone ahead of that. So it
is relevant and true at that point
whereas a spec is the spec. It's like
when you see the spec that is the that
is the final outcome. Um, very similar
to I guess when I'm prompting in in in a
Vive coding environment, my my prompt is
is relative to the the code as it was,
the code as it is after the prompt, and
it really connects those two those two
points in time. At any point afterwards,
the prompt that I use may not make any
sense because it only it it's only
referencing the point in time uh just
before I I sent that. So, yeah, very
aligned on that. Um, we've we've
mentioned specs a few times. I'd love to
go a little bit deeper. Um, Richard, I
bring you in here. What do we mean by a
specification?
>> Uh, okay. So, that's a very deep
question. Um, depending on who you're
who you're talking to. Um, and maybe
maybe I'll start as something that
Nikquil was just talking about here. We
weren't necessarily looking to to build
yet just another AI or IDE tool or
something like this, right? We're really
kind of trying to to to help people
shape software development in their
practices for the future. Um, and
there's a lot of things in software
engineering that have existed since, you
know, 40s, '50s, 60s that we're just now
seeing to to come into play today,
right? Like specifications as a as a
term. A lot of people usually have in
their head, you know, some sort of
formal method that they're that they're
talking about, especially when you get
deeper in systems and and usually
they're talking about certain things
like safety properties or livveness
properties of your system, right? Is it
making progress moving towards a goal or
are you violating these certain
properties? And and as you just
mentioned, Simon, that's super difficult
to tell in code just by looking at it.
Uh especially as you trace through a
large program or microservices, right?
If I want to if I want to make sure that
I have something like a read after write
property of my overall system, you can't
just glance at an if statement and
determine that in a really complex
program. You actually need to lift that
up to a higher level of uh kind of
definition for people to see what this
means of your system. And then as you're
executing the program, you need to make
sure that this certain invariant or
something is respected throughout the
system. So traditionally the way that
this has been done in software
engineering is uh is kind of a backwards
process actually. You build these
implementations um and you know as
software engineering has become more
common domain in the past 20 years or
so. Lots of people are really good at
those low-level implementations of such
but then when it comes to actually
believe it or not like people that work
on their systems actually can't reason
about them very well. So you bring then
these next level computer science PhD
experts that have knowledge of this
esoteric uh you know first order logic
modeling language whether that's TLA or
something like Daphnia that AWS uses or
P or something else um you you have
those those very esoteric experts that
are then walk backwards from the system
and they build these models to to do
verification or or some sort of
validation on the system as well.
Um so what we are trying to do here you
know to your question of what are
specifications we kind of want to make
this approachable for any developer to
really have this power right and I think
that's a a super important top level
point because many times when it comes
to AI tools there's an an overabundance
of talking about well now we can make
programming available to anybody that
didn't know how to code that's true we
can also make reasoning about systems
and new tools available ailable to even
those developers that didn't know how to
code before and were kind of the super
developers before. Now they have
compounding power that they can bring to
their practices that they really didn't
have before.
>> Yeah, really interesting actually how
that how it brings it. It's really going
to open it up in terms of it's more of a
creator now, right? You don't actually
the the point of a developer isn't now
who can actually write the best code.
It's who can create the most, you know,
through uh through business logic
essentially being able to communicate
better uh will actually become almost
the the the better developer versus
versus their understanding of the the
underlying implementation. And if you
take it into more of a philos
philosophical kind of like motivation, I
know when we talked previously, we would
we were talking about specifications
into into a much more of a philos
philosophical layer. talk us a little
bit about the the the the philosophical
motivation behind
>> Yeah, I guess that's the term dour.
Yeah. So, let's let's talk about that a
little bit and tie it to your previous
question, right? So, what are specs kind
of, right? You could say specs are this
technical artifact and there's lots of
different ways that that people build
specifications historically. Um what it
re my answer would be a specification is
about behavior talking about the
behavior of the system rather than
implementation. Right? Um now
historically and and philosophically
that showed up in lots of different
ways. um you know uh there's been
different types of uh the most common
specification known in the industry is
something like design by contract and
this is usually where you have this if
you look at the research this
style logic of saying like I have this
precondition of my function and these
are the the mathematical quantifiers it
needs to meet like can only take an
integer within this domain and then the
post condition of that it must meet this
and then you might define like a
termination condition or a loop
invariant um that has to hold
inductively if you're familiar with the
terms and so forth. That's that's the
real like sort of like um program
enforcing the contracts of like your
functions and so forth. Um a lot of the
the newer stuff as well like if you've
ever heard of lean from Amazon around
like specifications, these are more
theorem based which is I I would I would
say gives you a bit more fidelity like
even a lower level primitive of
something like that. um to where you you
sort of have this this uh it's it's
based on on um dependent type theory
where you have a correspondence between
types in your programs themselves how
they tie into logic right now this is
important of why I'm going into this
around the research and theory of this
and how this brings to hero because
those are artifacts that people would
build with really in those formal
languages and I mentioned specs are
about behavior in what you're doing and
so Nik will demo here in a minute really
like from Kira's perspective, we try to
walk through that at even a higher level
so that as we evolve this system, we can
meet these different constraints, right?
So when you build with Kira, you're
seeing a top level requirements. Well,
if you look at this, this is actually
something known as a EARS syntax. Um,
this is easy approach to requirement
syntax. And this wasn't just like a a
clever thing that we figured out with
auto formalization to tie a prompt into
how you define requirements. It's
actually an extension of temporal logic
which is an extension of first order
logic. So this gives us a lot of power
behind the scenes on being able to
control what the model does, how we
verify certain parts of the process, how
we build the design and then that h how
that leads to the implementation itself.
And the interesting innovation here is
when we tie that to the UX, then you're
actually allow able to bring ground
truths to your system, right? So
philosophically what motivated a lot of
this uh was two kind of highlevel points
and you t you actually believe it or not
Simon kind of touched upon them before.
Um there's a a computer science
professor um I think he's actually in
the UK uh believe it or not Lawrence Tre
um where he talks about two issues with
building software and and as I go
through these also you'll we'll be able
to talk about how we ran into that
inside of Amazon when we were building
this. Um so one is what we usually talk
about the surf circular specification
problem. So this this means like to you
almost need to really build something
completely in order to specify it,
right? That's that's how you know what
you want it to be but then you're trying
to specify something so that you can say
what the implementation is right so it
goes back and forth. The other is this
observer effect when you do this right
like the act of actually seeing the
software changes not only how we but
also others think the software should
act. Um and that even might be us
changing how we look at it over time. So
these sort of things are really why I I
like in Curo this sort of vibe mode and
spec mode as well, right? Like you can
build it and vibe it and now you can
specify it. Now you can go back and
forth. So you get this sort of interplay
on how humans act.
>> Yeah. Really, really, really curious and
I think it does, you know, when we think
about in software development today, how
much even a prototype or something like
that helps our understanding of how
something should be built. uh and you
know the way we do iterative programming
today through agile methodologies and
things like that we're constantly
learning as we go and it makes complete
sense like you know I'm sure if 10 15
years ago or gosh maybe closer to 25
years ago pre-aggile um if we was to
think about uh you know writing specs
more in a waterfall style it would make
a ton more sense then in comparison to
how we build software today uh the vibe
and the the um the vibe and the spec
kind of mode are super a super cool as
well in Kira. I think maybe maybe we
should maybe we should jump in and
should we should we jump into demo and
actually see this because I think uh
it'll it'll very much help uh for our
viewers to to see this. Uh for those who
are viewing on podcast only on audio
only do check us out on either YouTube
and I believe uh on Spotify as well you
can see the video uh through the the
stream on Spotify uh but it's on YouTube
in full. It's probably the easiest way
to easiest way to view it. So, Nikil, I
think you're going to show us the uh the
demo, right?
>> So, let's actually go ahead and look at
Kuro and see how this works. So, KO uh
what we did is we took a it's a fork of
COSS.
Uh but really what we did that so we
could really build an experience that we
could fully control uh from a from a
user experience perspective. So as you
see here is I have this uh I have this
tab here for KO um which is show shows
you that the the the core features that
we offer. So off the bat you see there's
a specs folder as a structured way to
build features.
Uh there's hooks which I'll actually get
into a little bit later but hooks are
almost like an infosa. Uh you can set up
hooks to basically watch your uh watch
your codebase and make changes um if if
certain files are touched.
Steering. So steering bas allow what
steering does it allows you to set rules
and guide your agent every time you
every time you interact with the agent
whether you're interacting with them via
vibe or spec you can set steering rules.
So often what I do is when I'm starting
with a new with a existing project, the
first thing I do with Kira is I generate
the steering docks and the steering docs
give you essentially they get
autogenerated and they give you like a
product overview of what what they
analyze your codebase and give you a
product overview of what what it is.
Uh it looks at all the different um
files and and and and builds an
understanding of the project. So as you
can see there's like here's what the
root directory is. Here's how it's
organized. This is an nextjs app. Here's
where the data layer is. Here's the
state management, the type definitions,
and there's a text stack file. Also the
text app here for this application I'm
using um it's just a react application
uh with vit and it's got command it's
got some information on what pack what
what build tooling is installed
>> and and is this is this something that
you would kind of like expect to perhaps
even uh put into some kind of source
control that you know the rest of the
team can use and and if you have an
organization you can all kind of like
you know work within a rule set to uh to
to adhere to.
>> Absolutely. So uh right now with
steering we have steering files defined
at a repository level. So all these
files are actually in your repository.
So if I switch to the explorer view
you'll see there's this curo folder here
and essentially everything is in so the
steering files are actually just
markdown files right uh so you can check
them in and you can add your own custom
markdown file. So what you know a good
example would be let's say you have
certain rules on how you want your UI to
if you're generating UI for components
your UI needs to follow these
requirements right it needs to let's say
you need to use tailwind classes you
need to uh the styling needs to be
certain ways enforced by like the
marketing team so it allows you to for
your team for you to define a structure
of how you operate. A big feature
request we've been getting from early
customers is hey we have actually
multiple teams uh that need to align on
um you know certain rules uh how do you
how do we how do we define that and
that's something that's that's you know
also coming soon and and something that
we're actively thinking about
>> one one thing to note as Nikil goes into
the specs too all these things he's
showing are fully composable in the
system and what I mean by that is hooks
can trigger at spec workflow stages as
you like it for matching file globs and
so forth. Similarly, steering can
actually uh mention dox in spec
workflow. So like a common thing that a
lot of customers do is they're like well
I actually want to augment my
implementation so that it follows TDD
for example. You can create a steering
file that will do this with whatever
your TDD rules are. Then you go about
your spec workflow and it will respect
that.
>> Yeah. I mean I can quickly even show
that here. Right. So all I do is I say
augment
my workflow to ensure that we're
following
TDD best practices.
And then I just hit refine and and Kira
takes that. And now what it's going to
do is it's going to say, hey, I'm going
to take this I'm creating this new
steering file and'll actually like
update my lazy prompt to make it a more
to make it a more effective prompt. Um,
so as you can see here, so there's an
inclusion also. So I can there are
different states for this inclusion. I
can set it to manual or always include,
right? That um so took my single prompt
and now I have like essentially a new
file that to guide the agent.
>> Awesome. That's that's super powerful. I
love that almost like turning it from a
brief into a spec. That's uh that's
>> Yeah, we see spec and steering very much
uh uh kind of they play together really
well.
Uh and uh and yeah, so actually let's
let's actually just walk walk through
specs now. So for the application that I
have right now, I've got reviews. I also
I added a cart cart once before. Um I've
got these I've got this heart icon here,
but I don't actually have any way to add
f to um well I've got this this heart
icon here, but that doesn't actually do
anything. It doesn't actually work. uh
so I can add something to my favorites.
Um what I'm what I will do now is maybe
build a new spec about hey I'm building
this this mechanism to add to favorites
and we'll walk through that experience.
So what I'm going to do first I'm going
to go ahead and say hey I want to create
a spec. I'm going to enter an idea here
and I'll say um I want to uh add the
ability
to favorite
um
items in my
uh in my app.
So what that's going to do now is it's
going to go ahead and create a new
favorite system
spec. And with that you can see the
agent is is creating a requirements
MD file. And again all of this is it's
just marked down. You know one one of
our tenants for at least our first
launch was to build something that had
opinions but make it pretty flexible so
users can tailor this to you know
different formats. Again with steering
if I have if I have some different
formats the way I want to generate this
I can do this do that but we have
sensible defaults.
And so this is the this is the
requirements phase. Is that right?
>> Yep. We're in the requirements phase. So
like it took the it took that initial
prompt I had which was you know kind of
really badly defined for a PM I might
say
uh but had the ability to favorite items
and then it went ahead and generated a
requirements file for me. So let's
actually go through the requirements a
little bit. So we have an introduction.
Each requirement has a user story with
acceptance criteria.
Now this is then the acceptance criteria
is what we have in years format. Now
this is something that I actually uh
from my years as a PM have found really
find really useful. So if you're not
folks are not familiar how Amazon works,
Amazon has this process of uh PRFAQ
writing where we essentially building a
new product. We write a PR FAQ and then
that PRFQ goes gets implemented and you
build that out. But often there's a lot
of information context that the PRFQ is
not able to capture like the details and
the edge cases about how how these
systems are meant to operate and the
best way I found to do that working with
uh engineering teams is that you break
things into user stories and acceptance
criteria. So the user stories is almost
like the highle definition. So as a
customer browsing products
I want to mark items as favorites so
that I can find them easily without
having to search again. Right? That's
that's the traditional definition of a
user story that everyone can understand.
Now when you if as a PM you give that
user story to an engineering team
there's like a lot of questions around
it right there's like uh how how is it
meant to work in in in a scenar like
let's just think about this this
favorites use case right so with with
favorites when I when I add something as
a favorite right um if a if a can a user
click and and and andclick it to unfavor
right is there uh is there a count that
needs to be displayed of how many
favorites I have right like if you
actually start building out the the
feature, there's a lot of details and
and nuances that go into almost every
feature you build uh as as a developer.
So, uh so over here is we've got the
first one around marking items and the
acceptance criteria in yours format is
when a user views a product card and the
system shall display a heart icon and
then there's there's something around
click and and not click
and then I want to be able to view all
my favorite items in one place. That's
the second one.
You know this is a good example of an
edge case that when the favor list is
empty then the system shall display an
appropriate empty state. Uh you know
what you can do here is I can actually
um say like you know
uh and I can edit this either here or I
can edit this in chat. I can be like u
you know make so for for requirement
four where there's an empty empty state
I can be like okay uh make sure that
this experience
has some uh iconography. All right.
So I can do this here or I can do this
in in in in chat.
So this is really the way so you know as
a as a team you can iterate on
requirements before you move ahead right
so um the third one is I want my
favorites to persist across browser
sessions that's another like user story
that you know my my simple user story
didn't think about uh favorite count
indicator
>> and when you edit it just then you you
do do you do you prefer the the LLM to
edit the spec or how how much
>> um so what I what I sometimes do is that
I'll I'll just I I prefer I personally
prefer the LM to edit it but really like
I can I can you know if I have a new one
I can just add it here right um and we
have autocomplete as a feature so it
will it'll start as I type as you can
see there's something already just
appeared so I can start typing and it'll
it'll kind of continue me personal my
personal preferences I I I I do what I
just did. But I'll also sometimes use
chat and say hey for uh you know I don't
like for example let's say
I don't really care about a count
indicator. Uh so I I'll just be like I
don't really care about the count
indicator requirement. Right? So this is
I'm almost vive coding the requirements
right now. Think about it. Right? So I I
just find that the easiest. Um, and you
know there's there's still a lot of lot
of room for improvement here. Like you
know one of the things that we're
thinking of is how do we make these
easier to gro like how do you make the
acceptance criteria more easier to gro
so you know that so users can review
them and like understand you know to
Richard's earlier point if two
requirements have like conflicting kind
of information. uh how do we uh h how
does the user be how is the user made
aware of it so they don't miss it
>> or in a or in a larger team uh like
multiple people could view what you know
the three of us what NIL is going
through here even if he had you know 10
15 20 requirements let's say that it's
part of a larger system and you want to
compare these together to see if there's
logical contradictions uh that that's
some of the area that uh that we're
looking towards in the future as well
because you really want these in team
workflows as you're as you're building
them to keep keep the projects moving
smoothly.
>> Yeah. So yeah, as you can see, I think
it it went ahead and removed the that
that requirement for count.
Um, so I'm just going to say, okay,
things this looks good. I'm going to go
ahead and move to the design phase. So
the requirements is very much more is
very much about the kind of like the
what. So this is defining what we're
trying to build. Is the design much much
more about the kind of like leaning into
the how now about how it's going to
start building this into an application
or is it more about the architecture?
How does this work?
>> Absolutely. It's it's it's about how the
the requirements for the W and the
design is the how. So I'm going to go
ahead and say okay let's move ahead and
let's let's go create the design. Now
what what Kuro is going to do is it's
actually looking at the existing code
base in order to determine what the
design needs to be. So as you can see
it's reading a bunch of files and then
it say okay I'm going to create now this
design markdown file right that will get
generated again based on the the
requirements. Great. So the system went
ahead and created a design. Now you know
the the process we've been piloting uh
on Kirro now is that we're like we're
we're heavily dog fooding uh Kirro
internally is that we're trying to take
the requirements and design. So let's
say we're building a new feature like we
have an upcoming like point feature to
do. Let's let's gen let's generate the
specs for it. Let's generate the
requirements. Let's generate the design
all within the codebase
and then take those as artifacts and sit
with the sit with the team and and
decide whether um those look good or
not. Like you know a lot of the time we
actually spend as a team especially when
you work in teams they could be small
teams or large teams is is kind of
ironing out the details of the the
details of the design and and and and
the requirements. So in this case what
we typically do um it hasn't done it
here but like if you're typically
building a feature we generate like a
system diagram. So I, you know, I can
ask it to do it. It'll do it. But in
general, it's saying, "Hey, here's what
the architecture is." So we've got, um,
you know, here's here's state management
patterns. Here's the core components and
interfaces. So it's going to add like
this favorites context type. Um, add to
favorites, remove favorites. Uh, here's
the components. There are already these
components. We're going to enhance them.
Here are new components that are needed.
And um, and you know, here's like our
data model. Right now we're using a
local data model. So it's it's uh it's
like adding new interfaces to the data
model.
Uh error handling and testing
strategies.
So it's thinking through we got to we
got to handle errors. Let's let's think
about testing. Uh and and here's what
our here's what our implementation
approach is going to look like. Right?
So I can I can go ahead and edit these
things. um you know before like over
here I've already kind of I'm done a
path where I'm adding a feature to an
existing application. Often times what I
do is I say hey I actually don't want
this new if I if I don't want a new
interface or if I'm like hey you
you're actually you're actually
generating something that is um that I
like let's say for example I I I want to
focus on uh unit testing and not
integration testing for now. I can go
ahead and and make make those edits. Uh
but so this whole process is meant to be
the initial start of the process. So
where you say, okay, this is where I'm
going to start and this is where I'm
going to I'm going to review with my
team. If there are trade-offs that I
need to make, I'll I'll I'll kind of add
those trade-offs here and and make a
decision with my team on how I want to
proceed.
>> And and what happens when there are
conflicts between your let's say your
design and your requirements? So there
if there are conflicts with your design
and requirements here right now um
they're they're basically manually
resolved. Typically your requirements do
not your requirements and designs are
like your design is reflected in your
requirements. So I can walk through like
the process of how you iterate through
through both right so you know when when
I go back to a feature I can say hey I
actually want to now add this new
requirement to this feature. uh let's
say the thing that I removed count,
right? I could go back and add count and
then we'll go through the process of
updating the design as well to take into
account the new requirement.
>> But let let's actually talk about this
one for a second. This is a good point.
Um so the the process that we do is uh
we we use the the generated requirements
along with other context engines and
then some uh some things on the back end
inside of the the KO API that AWS hosts
to to sort of curry these things as they
go forward. Right? So using that
information from the requirements build
the design using that the next phase NIL
will show the task list and so forth.
Now we a customer could modify their
design with something that violated one
of the requirements and it would still
go ahead as they go to the next step and
build the uh implementation plan.
But we kind of assert as we were
building this over the last year and
working with people that's okay, right?
Because the alternative could be let's
say that somebody did something and we
went back and verified against the
requirements and and it it violated
something, right? That's actually a
pretty bad developer experience, right?
And this is what happens in the real
world. Like sometimes you actually have
more domain knowledge than what you can
encode in a document, right? And and
what you see a lot of times with tools
is when they try to put these rigid
structures in place, you can't do this
or go down this path. it actually ends
up compounding and having a lot of
friction for customers. Uh we got a new
visitor in the back there. Um so uh
uh so we took the choice that we want to
give the customers flexibility here in
what they can do rather than restrict
them from an action.
>> Um so then let's get to the final stage
of this process. So uh we've you know as
you can see there's a requirements file
we just created. as a design file. And
now what we're going to do is we're
going to go ahead and and get to a list
of tasks.
So what the task is the task list is
really the implementation plan. So how
do you take the requirements and design
and break it into like discrete
uh items that you as a user can execute
against? So you know this workflow if I
was if I was vi coding this workflow
right I would have started with the
prompt that I had up top. it would have
it it would have generated something and
then I would have kept kept kind of
iterating through but now now what I've
got is I've essentially got a task.md
file and as you can see here it's broken
my my it's taken my design and actually
broken it into individual implementation
tasks. So the first one is create
favorites context and hook
infrastructure.
Add the favorites view to the main
application routing.
Create a list component for displaying
favorite favored products. Then it's
enhancing it's enhancing individual
components
and uh it's doing things like
accessibility tests. So it's really
thinking through this very thoroughly
like I would you know if I was v coding
this I would I would probably not think
of accessibility. Um right. um error
handling, edge case management,
>> and and how much of these how much of
these tasks are for the LLM versus the
user? I mean, if I was to, you know, is
this something that that you would
really want me to come in and maybe add
to, or is this something whereby it adds
structure that then allows the LLM to
processes in a in a in an orderly manner
that it can actually it can actually do
it properly? What what's the what's the
user interaction with this file? Yeah.
So the user interaction with this file
is that it's I I think it's I think it's
the latter based off of what you said
but uh is that it's it's providing some
structure for how you engage with the LM
cuz the structure really helps. I mean
that's been our experience that's been
the experience of a lot a lot of our
early testers as well is that the
structure really helps it do helps it
implement tasks well and and complete
and in in a complete manner.
Right? So, I'm going to say this task
list. Again, I can because we, you know,
as Richard said, we indexed for
flexibility. I can go ahead and edit
this task list and remove a bunch of
things if I wanted to um to kind of if I
wanted to say, hey, I actually don't
want to do this or I I don't want to do
I don't want to enhance the product
detail component, for example, right?
But I'm going to go go ahead and
finalize this task list. And now um you
know this is kind of some of the unique
unique UI elements we built into this
experience. As you can see there's a
there's each of these have a start task
button. Very intentionally we you know
one of the first early feedbacks we got
from people was like hey can you have a
play all button? We've we've been
staying away from it because what we've
observed with user testing is that as
you kind of incrementally build things
with with editors, you have better
understanding as to what's happening,
right? Um, so I'm going to go ahead and
hit start task here. And what that does
is, as you can see, it changes the UI
here to say, okay, your task is in
progress. And and
it's going to go ahead and implement the
task. And as a user, what I can do is I
can I can be on top I can be on top of
what's being done. Right? So if I if I
uh follow the changes being done,
what what it'll show me is is adding all
these different it'll it'll add
basically I think we're building out the
the the underlying infrastructure if you
will for this favorites context
uh to be done and I can see all the
changes very easily see all the changes
that are being made. So, you know, we're
adding some sort of mock storage.
There's a test component. So, it's
starting with like a test file.
>> I' I'd love to almost like see an LLM
interact with this whereby it's not
necessarily a human click and the start
task, but it's more driven by an LLM
effectively as a judge as well as a
orchestrator. That that could be super
interesting to to to see how how
accurately it would almost imitate or
simulate a human looking at the looking
at the output.
Yeah. Yeah. Abs. Absolutely. I think
that's a feature that that's a that's an
interesting feature request that we've
we've uh we've seen um where I think
what you're saying is that hey, I've got
a bunch of tasks here. Can the LM can I
can I offload this to an LLM to to
handle, right? That's that's what you're
that's what you're maybe maybe a
slightly more async workflow. Is that
kind of
>> Mhm. Yeah. Pretty much. Pretty much. So
what it's doing now is that it's
actually installing um it's using
justest. It's actually setting up a
testing framework as well. Uh I think
it's because I added the TDD rule.
That's why it's it's it's doing this up
front. Uh because it was part of my
steering. But while this is happening,
let me just actually walk through maybe
the
maybe like how this hap what what the
state looks like at the end. Right? So
once once a task is completed as a user
I am able to view
um
I'm I'm able to view the the actual
changes. So I'm able to say okay here's
what so this was my earlier example
where I was able to view what changes
happened and so I kind of have full
context over each of the tasks as to as
to what the LLM did for or what the
agent did rather for the individual
task. So I'm as a you know there there
there's while it's doing things for me I
have kind of full oversight over what's
being done.
>> You also notice the requirements on
here. This is this is an important piece
of just the full software development
life cycle. This is the the concept of
requirements tracing. Right? So this is
how we document and track the
relationships throughout the entire
state machine that's executing these
things including as we curry the one
task to another and process this
implementation plan. So if I were to now
go back to let's say the requirements
and I were to make a change to one of
those requirements would it would it
look into the design and task list
identify the relation I guess between
those three and then say okay I only
need to actually make updates to the
ones that have the references to the um
to those requirements that were changed.
>> Yeah let's go ahead and do that. Let's
say um you know I want to add like
requirement you know I for
counting the fe favorites right
now the the the thing is I don't need to
I don't really need to define the this
in like the proper format I just hit
refine.
So now what what this refine button will
do is that'll look at this file and and
see um I think we have oh I I have I
have a hook cued. So actually before I
do this maybe it's a good segue to I was
like why why is this execution cued? Uh
do you see this agent hook thing
spinning here?
>> Ah I see. Yeah.
>> So what I have is I have a documentation
updater. Uh so hooks are a feature that
that allow that that basically watch
your repository for different events.
Right now we have file create, file
save, file delete and manual trigger
events. Uh so what manual trigger does
is that it basically says okay just
manually trigger this. uh and it's
almost like a like an enforcer right
like that says okay uh at the end of an
when a file is touched do x right so in
this case I have if if you've created
new typescript files in the source
folder uh update update the the docu the
documentation and I think that's
effectively what this hook this hook is
doing
Um,
yeah. So that that's that's that's what
this hook is is meant to do. It's it's
the documentation updator. So it'll go I
I have a readme file in this repository
and it's going to go ahead and and
update that. So I I'm able to create a
whole variety of hooks. And the way we
see customers using hooks is really is
really interesting. So here I have
another hook where I've got this
component SRP validator. So when
whenever new React components are added,
make sure they're like well defined and
like they don't handle multiple
concerns. So as a team I can enforce
these practices across across my team.
So even when we come up with the design,
right, that that uh we are we are
actually making the right decisions. Let
me just switch back to the design view
for my spec. And um Richard, I think you
want wanted to add something here.
>> Yeah. So, another piece that's
interesting here that I just like to
call out is is is probably my favorite
feature here, especially for experienced
software engineers is you might be
looking at this and uh looking at this
code snippet or a section of the error
handling defined in this doc or
something else and being like I know
from my institutional knowledge this is
this is how I should change this
interface or I or additionally I want
some other data structure in here or
something else. Um so what we actually
built is a uh context LSP that is
integrated in the IID as well as this uh
interface as well. So um for example if
NIL were to just in anywhere in the
markdown here just uh put um a pound
sign
and you'll see this is actually giving
you a context reference and if he hits
enter it's pointing to a file. So, a
common thing uh you could imagine like
this design doc could get really big
over time or you've got common designs
that you want to include sort of like a
library import of sorts into multiple
designs that you've got over time. So,
you could actually inject that into here
and then as KO goes through these
phases, it will respect it as it's
building out your implementation plan.
Like a great example of this that that I
use a lot in mine is uh property based
testing. And property based testing is a
very sophisticated technique that u
allows you to kind of have a spectrum of
correctness in your system, right? It's
not full proofbased, but it's much more
than just unit tests or even
implementation um or integration tests I
should say, right? And what's pretty
cool is will create just little markdown
files for the specific language that I
have. like if I'm writing in Python,
hypothesis is a great uh property based
testing library and I'll say like this
is the structure that I want and then I
can say what the properties are right
like these are the properties that I
want to hold which humans are really
good at and then the model will actually
do the quantification of that into code
and then when you actually go through
running your test then you get CPUs that
execute that with all the fuzzing and so
forth. So this is a super powerful
feature that encouraged a lot of people
as they're building advanced systems to
to to take full advantage of themselves
>> and and where people where people want
to you know they get through to the
implementation and then all of a sudden
they think oh actually I'd love to
change this this thing um let's say it's
and it is a implementation detail let's
say of course when we do something like
that code becomes the source of truth
versus the versus the spec and then how
do we how do we regenerate and so forth
um how does that cause problems and how
what what's the best way of kind of
avoiding developers touching code?
>> I would say we don't really uh see that
as a problem if they want to touch code.
Um now it is possible yeah the uh the
specification can drift a little bit uh
from where the code is. Um,
I would say uh that space is going to
evolve in the future and we've got some
ideas about how to handle that in a
little bit more robust way right now,
but I wouldn't discourage engineers from
editing code. In fact, if you think
about it, we're in a way encouraging
them by offering both the spec and the
vibe mode. So, if you are an expert and
you know targeted changes you want to
make to your system, by all means, go
ahead and vibe those small pieces.
>> Right. Right. So, so a spec a spec then
is um if we think about life cycles, how
long is the life cycle of a spec? Is it
the life cycle of the change um versus
you know more than the life cycle of a
of an app if if uh people want to change
code?
>> Yeah, this is this is a tough question
too. It's I I would my common answer is
I think about it like comments in code,
right? If you put comments in code at
that point in time, it's temporal and
they will hold as people and teams edit
them over time. Um, they can drift. That
is true. Um, so you have to think about
it as a similar artifact in your system
um and and build controls around it.
>> Um, one thing we haven't talked about
here on this screen is uh on the bottom
left, Nick, uh, MCP servers. um h what's
the what's the best way of uh kind of
like making the most out of MCP servers
or other other services around uh from
within Kira?
>> Yeah. So uh MCP servers work with all
the features. So whether you're vibing
or you're specking MCP servers will will
work. So in this case I have the fetch
MCP server which will allow me which
actually allows me to do a web search.
So if I when I'm building a feature
especially even in the design phase I
can be like hey can you can you search
the web for what the best practices are
regarding um regarding like you know
maybe like maybe it's a framework or
like maybe it's a a technology you can
you can do that so we have full MCP uh
local MCP support so you can add you can
add any MCP so server so uh to via via
like a JSON file that we have here and
you can do that with the chat or you can
just update it yourself and and then
those MCB servers get invoked by the
agent and the agent can decide whether
in spec mode or vibe mode whether um the
agent needs to be invoked.
>> So so so for example um if if we do
provide a uh I don't know a docs
creation uh MCP server of course the LLM
can do doc creation by itself as well.
Do you find any challenges between when
uh like the user wants you to use an MCP
server uh but actually it's trying to
it's trying to uh do it itself because
the LLM has capability to an extent to
perform that action. Uh do you ever have
do you ever see contention between
whether it does that?
>> I mean I think basically what you're
saying is if there's an MCP server
that's overlapping with one of your
hooks functionality.
>> Yeah. Or even just a basic LLM
capability.
>> Uh absolutely. I I think that you you
can you can see that happen. And then I
think part of again the way the system
is built is is that it's it's flexible
enough for you to interrupt when working
with agents basically you're working
with systems that are not like
non-deterministic in nature right so you
need to make as from a UX affordance you
need to make sure that you've got the
right level of flexibility so users can
interrupt the agent like for example I
could have interrupt the agent while
it's while it was going and tell it hey
actually you need to do this instead.
Um, so that that that's all all all
possible with Kira.
>> Yeah. And I presume even add it into the
task itself to say d I want you to use
this service or this tool to to to
create me the documentation for this or
within the uh within the hooks. Yeah.
Okay. So let's let's talk about let's go
back into talking about uh specs just a
little bit more. Um and and and and
Richard I guess um I guess the specs
that you kind of showed which which
realistically is is a number of
different things. It's the is the
requirements, the design, the tasks, all
of that I guess together is is in
combination the specification in the KO
world. um in terms of um you know where
we are today versus where you started. I
suspect you learned a a ton of things
going through kind of like maybe the
private betas using it internally at
AWS. Uh what are the some of the key
learnings that you've that you took from
from this journey of of learning about
specifications? So a few things um you
know we mentioned and you kind you you
nailed it like specifications are kind
of the combination of those artifacts in
the curo product right but high level
like we talked about they're about
behavior and and really our view on this
is uh in a learning is they need to be
kind of composable documents with like
really functional business use cases as
well as code pseudo code people can put
in there technical diagrams behaviors
around error handling behaviors around
properties, right? And so some learnings
there like um I I I mentioned when we
kicked off this podcast like there was
building the hero product and then the
research phase also that was kind of
parallel and they joined up. Um let's
kind of talk about this and how this
went especially what we haven't
mentioned. Um, so I'll start some of
this and then hand it over to Nikil to
talk about this is like
there was a few iterations of Spack
internally that were big failures first.
So we proved what wouldn't work actually
too, right? So um you know I mentioned
uh we we've got a lot of um Amazon has
this automated reasoning group that's
well kind of known and we have uh you
know web pages on it and and they the
formal methods community dealt with a
lot of the same things that we in fact
they were inputs into how we built this
product itself. Um and they you know
early days of Amazon with these systems
um really where specifications were were
were highly used were some of the
systems backing AM and S3 and so forth
and um separate from the technology. My
biggest learning of talking through
those teams and and what they were
building was there was so much back and
forth between people and engineers,
right? Like you had people that were
experts on the implementation and then
experts on modeling the behaviors and so
forth. And I remember I saw this one
presentation internally and it was
actually like showing the paths between
the offices in like a triangle and how
the carpet was getting worn because what
you would do is you say all right we
define this behavior over here to work
like this and then go talk to the expert
on implementing IM or something it's not
exactly like that and you go back and
forth in here and that's really what
we're doing here right is allowing you
to iterate and go back on that system
and so um you know without sounding too
boring like a lot of this is you know
codified institutional knowledge and you
know SDLC practices but let's let's talk
about some of the things as we were
building this like we could have easily
said like uh you know what we're going
to reinvent that space even though
people have been building software and
and sort of like like force certain
patterns down people's throats and um so
one of them maybe and I'll hand this
over to Nikil that we tried at first um
and I touched upon how you could augment
your system to do this is like make
every spec go through a TDD flow. That
was one thing we tried at first here.
Um, so Nik Hill, you want to talk about
that a little bit?
>> Uh, yeah. I mean, I can talk I maybe
talk about that and then what we what we
did next. So I think the approach was
like, hey, let's start with TDD and TDD
is great. Um, like where you start with
tests and then based off the tests you
generate the code, right? And you know,
I think from our early tests, we found
that that generally worked pretty well.
uh but then when actually putting that
in front of users and customers it's not
it was not typically how they were like
people were working TDD is great if
people follow it but a lot of a lot of
us a lot of customers like we're just
are just not were not not doing that
that was not the logic chain they
followed so what that what that did is
it enforced a lot of rigidity in how
people use specs and the feedback we got
from users was that um this is not
really working for me,
right? And and then I think the second
thing the next thing we tried uh the
next major thing we tried is we said
okay uh the the experience for
generating a spec was you know you open
a file or or or a folder and you right
click on it and you say new spec and
then we generate like a effectively a
specification for what what's contained
in that folder. But that again was um
users found that it was it was
interesting. it was like generating like
you know an like information about
what's there but that's kind of like
what we have we have with steering right
so it was like okay how do I actually
action on this and build something new
right and I I think finally where we
landed was we we kind of those all the
learnings that Richard's been working on
as he's been working um you know on on
on the specification based approach with
yours ears requirements and and designs
and we also saw the field and how uh you
know power users had changed how they
were working with agents right like
there like there was a lot more planning
up front there was a lot more uh there
was more meticulous thinking up front
before before doing tasks and we learned
from them and we I think you know
basically tried to learn take take our
learnings that we go we we go that we we
built inhouse
and apply them with a user experience
that's very much front and centered
around uh the the development process
which is a requirements design and
implementation process right and that's
where we landed with the current
experience and then you know the moment
we shipped this we got a lot of positive
signal and of course there were tons
tons of issues uh in the experience when
we first built it and and what you're
seeing now is probably like four
iterations in um but the core of this
really is around like your require
requirements, your design, your
implementation plan. And I think a lot
of the questions you asked around how
how do I edit this, how do I keep this
in sync, how do I review it are all kind
of things that we are very much actively
thinking about, not just from a
underlying technology or capabilities
perspective or science perspective, but
also from a user experience perspective.
H how to make this how to make this uh
palatable to users?
>> Yeah. And and from that when we say
users, I guess there are going to be
multiple different personas going
forward in terms of who who has the most
opinion on each of these files. And I
guess when we think about I don't know
whether it's tasks versus requirements.
I guess we might see two different types
of people. Maybe more a PM style on the
requirements and maybe more an engineer
or someone some some uh kind of like
development practitioner who cares more
about how things are built. Do you see
do you see different owners maybe going
forward with these different types of um
uh files as part of the spec?
>> Absolutely. Which is which is why I was
saying what we're doing is we're kind of
dog fooding this internally cuz we have
PMs owning like the requirements you
know engineering owning design. How do
how do we put them in places where
they're easy to share? Like a a top a
big feature request for we've been
hearing is that hey you know we have we
have some requirements in Jira or we
have some requirements in Asana. How do
we bring how do we how do we bring those
in and surface them, right? Um from a
and I think from a problem perspective
that's very interesting, right? Um how
do you how do you kind of make the
coordination of that that better? How do
you how do you like short circuit how do
you like save a bunch of upfront time
that goes into this requirements and
design planning uh in a way that makes
in a way that makes sense for how teams
operate, right? like we don't expect
every team to like PMs on every team to
be inside a code editor for example to
do things. So we have to kind of look at
how people are doing things in in in in
the wild and and enable them in the
tools that they're they're also using.
>> Absolutely. Um let's look a little bit
further forward as well before we before
we wrap in terms of where does this
where does this space lead? What's the
what's the next step do you feel for uh
from a from a spec oriented way? How do
you see people in future wanting to use
specifications or development with
specifications?
>> Uh Richard, do you want to take that
first?
>> Yeah, I'll start and uh then hand back
to you Nikil on this. Like so NL's been
talking about uh you know uh a lot of
the the coordination that which is
really the hard part, right? that you do
a lot of uh with a lot of teams and
products and so forth and um you know
there there's there's there's topics
around that that he could talk a lot.
The the one that's the most interesting
to me I mean there's there's obviously
some other things that we're going to do
with uh giving you more controls about
being able to see the ambiguity in the
process and you know contradictions like
we talked about before and um you know
also give you more entry points to this
workflow and so forth. Um th those are
all technical feature specifics and um
you know components of this
specification component that we'll do.
Um what I think is the most interesting
of where the the effect of a of a tool
like this of what it does is um in some
ways it shifts your focus from the
postbuilding phase into the code review
phase, right? Um because you know agents
and models build a lot of different uh
um
code bases and lines of code and so
forth. Um they're getting quite good and
refined at these things. Um no matter
what the AI detractors say, uh they they
they are quite um coming along further
um to to really meet some some high
standards, especially a lot of the
benchmarks that we've seen. Um, and
you've now got these code bases and
requirements and you have teams and
people that need to reason about
components of them, right? And that
could be reasoning about the or
reviewing even um efficiently in teams
the the refactoring parts of a program,
right? or it could be about reviewing
and reasoning about uh the new feature
parts of the component or even like the
secure security components right of of
code of implications of code changes
that are made. So I think that this is
going to be a real highlighted area not
just you know in hero but as the
industry as a whole over the next couple
years that really is untouched right now
in the in sort of the AI and editor
space. Uh yeah, I mean I I think for for
me right like I I think about it from
like the problems that um we have as
teams, right? Like look across the SDLC
process, right? So like I already kind
of talked a little bit about the upfront
process on like the back and forth with
like finalizing requirements and
designs. How do you have multiple when
you have multiple teams working together
like it gets even harder and more
complicated, right? How do how do we
kind of improve that process, right? And
then you know going going forward uh
past past the review once something is
out in the wild and there are issues how
do we bring those issues back to the
back to the actual uh development team
right uh so that we're really looking at
this from a whole life cycle perspective
and uh you know you know there are core
things that are not going to change not
going to be impacted
by by AI in terms of the problems you
have right
You ship software, there'll be problems
with it. How do how do you get those
problem? How do you fix those problems?
You when you build software, there's
ambiguous requirements or design. How do
you solve how do you make that easier?
So, that's how we're looking at uh this
space and and problem solving in this
space.
>> Awesome. And where are we with the build
right now? It looks like we've just
completed uh I think this was uh was
this section four?
>> Yeah, we've completed a bunch of tasks.
Uh I've been I've been going going at it
while we uh do things. So as you like
one of the things that you see that's
happening is that it's actually being
very methodical with generating tests.
Um so you know it generating generating
updates. So like it like I just executed
a card for uh this pro enhanced product
card component with favorite
functionality. So it's actually like
making sure the tests are set up right.
And so let's actually see what it's done
now. So I've I've got uh it's added like
a so it's added a favorite here already.
So I can favorite things. Let's see if
they I don't know if this is Yep. Yep.
They're actually showing up as favorites
as well.
>> And remember this this one Nikil had
that steering file to use TDD first. So
it actually augmented his flow to do
some of these up front rather than
later.
>> Exactly. And you know I picked a
relatively easy feature. A lot of times
um people use these AI demos to say,
"Hey, build me a game or build me
something that are very much green
field, right?" But like the reason why I
picked an easy feature like like adding
favorites is not because is to show that
there's actually a lot that goes into
building favorites. It's not just like
you know a simple thing that you can add
to your your application. uh you have to
think that you you know having tests
making sure things are accessible uh
making sure like the the number of
scenarios that were covered here are
things that I would have not thought
about doing.
>> Yeah. And and the nice and the nice
thing is it's the tests that are added
and I'm sure the tests would have
equally been added if we didn't do the
TDD piece but probably you know after uh
towards the end of the tasks. It's it's
not you know the thing that we miss with
vibe coding is the ability to actually
validate and truly say yes this is all
working. I haven't regressed other
things. And the nice the nice flow about
this is tests are being built by
default. It's it's it's coming as part
of the package. Uh and it allows us to
validate every step of what we're what
we're doing through the through the
tasks.
>> Yeah, absolutely. And like the product
of that that the hook was that the uh I
had I had it update like the readme
file. So a lot of developers like the
readme file to stay updated. So, so as
you can see, it added like the favorites
to the the the favorites to the um to
the actual experience. And you know,
it'll keep this read me up to date. The
hooks experience is also is is one of my
favorite things cuz you can really like
do the same thing. You can, you know,
language localization is also a good
one. Like you add a new feature and you
want to make sure that your strings are
in different, you know, in different
languages, you can just have a hook for
that. So, we're really seeing customers
get creative with the the types of hooks
they're creating.
>> Yeah. And you just avoid that debt that
will typically follow you around when
you don't do these things uh as as well.
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> Amazing. Um this has been a this has
been a great demo. It's been really
really great fun chatting with you both
and um and congratulations as well on
all the success that Kira's had. uh from
what I from what I saw on uh on on
Twitter. I think it's in it's in a it's
in a waiting list right now just because
it's had such an inc impressive number
of uh downloads from from people wanting
to wanting to try it out. Uh what what
what would you what advice would you
give to people who want to who want to
play with it today?
>> Yeah. Uh we are so grateful for to
everyone trying to get on you know are
we you know we've got thousands of users
and we were trying to optimize the
experience for the users who have
access. That's why we added the weight
list and uh we're working very
diligently to to get people off the wait
list and you should be hearing something
from us very soon.
>> Awesome. And if you're interested,
kirao.dev, I believe, right?
>> Yep. kira.dev.
>> Kira.dev. And you can join the wait list
there. Wonderful. Uh Nikil and Richard,
it been an absolute pleasure. Very very
insightful. Thank you very very much for
sharing uh for sharing your knowledge as
well as as well as Kira and uh and the
demo. Um, for those watching online, uh,
sorry, for those listening only, uh, on
to the podcast, do check out the YouTube
video cuz it's there's a ton of value,
uh, in the demo that was, uh, that was
shown today. Really appreciate you both
joining. Thanks very much.
>> Thanks, Simon.
>> Thank you.
>> And thanks very much for listening and
tune in to the next episode.
[Music]